(Penny:)nope...
Oh, he's cute!
(Bernadette:)Doesn't a teardrop tattoo
(Bernadette:)mean he murdered someone?
(Penny:)And he's sad about it.
(Leonard:)Hey.
Hello.
Hey, I thought you were gonna be out late?
(Howard:)If you wanted me
to stay out later,
(Howard:)you should've given me
more spending money.
(Raj:)What are you guys up to?
(Bernadette:)We put Amy on a dating app,
(Bernadette:)and we're seeing
what's out there.
Oh, fun!
Let me see.
(Raj:)Uh, no...
(Raj:)no, uh, definitely not.
(Howard:)What was wrong
with that guy?
(Raj:)Uh, he's Indian.
(Raj:)We've already got one of those.
(Raj:)Ooh, we should
find a nice Latino.
It really round us out.
(Howard:)Hey, I want to try.
(Amy:)Uh, excuse me,
c-can I have my phone back?
(Howard:)Hang on, I'm trying
to find you
(Howard:)the next great
love of your life.
(Howard:)The man who will
father your children.
(Howard:)Okay, yes or no on white
guy with dreadlocks?
(all clamoring)